Guide to the Peter Newell Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- OVERSIZE
  - From Series VII. Howard McCormick
    - Prints
      - [Old man with jug, hat and cane, portrait of or after Harry Townsend] wood engraving (Box 254, Folder 3461)
      - [Pianist] wood engraving, n.d. (Box 254, Folder 3462)
      - [Southwest scene] wood engraving, n.d. (Box 254, Folder 3463)
    - Paintings
      - Evening (Hopi Buttes, 1st Mesa, Polacoa, Arizona) oil on canvas board, 8-1/4 x 10/1/4 in.; has Salmagundi Club Thumb-box exhibition label on verso (Box 255, Folder 3464)
      - Hopi Maiden gesso on board, 13-3/4 x 10/3/4 in.; framed and in fragile condition, 1940 (Box 255, Folder 3465)
      - Hopi Man gouache on paper, 10 x 8 in., 1908 (Box 255, Folder 3466)
- From Series VIII. Work by Other Artists, n.d.
  - Chapman, Charles [Man seated in kitchen, window open] inscribed lower right: "To Tony Baker from Charles S. Chapman, NA" (Box bsd, folder 3467)
  - Edwards, George Wharton "The Palace of Justice, Brussels," from "From Home to Throne in Belgium" by Clare de Graffenried, for Harper's Monthly, 1897 Apr (Box bsd, folder 3468)
  - Rhead, Louis "How Robin Hood did cheat the tinker", n.d. (Box bsd, folder 3469)
  - Street, Frank "Stevens #3 - He assisted slaves by defending them in the courts," for The Mentor (Box bsd, folder 3470)
  - Towles, G. Beverly [Golfer], n.d. (Box bsd, folder 3471)
  - Watson, Henry S. "At the Fourth Annual Sportsmen's Exhibition," for Harper's Weekly, 1898 Jan 29 (Box bsd, folder 3472)
- Cold Storage, n.d.
  Contains film negatives removed from Series III. Newell Family Photographs.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 256 (film negatives): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Box 197, folder 2434 (Box 256, Folder 3473)
  - Box 197, folder 2452 (Box 256, Folder 3474)
  - Box 199, folder 2470 (Box 256, Folder 3475)
  - Box 199, folder 2473 (Box 256, Folder 3476)
  - Box 200, folder 2498 (Box 256, Folder 3477)
  - Box 200, folder 2500 (Box 256, Folder 3478)
  - Box 200, folder 2508 (Box 256, Folder 3479)
  - Box 200, folder 2516 (Box 256, Folder 3480)
  - Box 200, folder 2525 (Box 256, Folder 3481)
  - Box 201, folder 2548 (Box 256, Folder 3482)
  - Box 201, folder 2550 (Box 256, Folder 3483)